Are we there are we in let me see this is I see stuff on the screen. Okay, so
This should work now. I think I set it up, right?
But I have the TTS setup at cultivistikey.com
I want to shout out Alexandra. She said she would give me a tripod to help upgrade my show. I think it's like
Awesome and thank you so much. It was like the world's crazy where you can just open my door
And I was like I almost stripped over. Oh my god. It was there. I opened my door. So thank you so much
I just want to shout out. Thank you so much for this work up is working great. If it is full
It is a high level. I think
I think it could be a little higher. I don't know. I had like a little like a
Fanking girl like that, right?
But see what I needed to do. I need to log into this real quick because
i cannot see information yet but i hope i look okay and so this uh this is like a not stream
yard connected and maybe i'll figure out how to do that eventually i'm just happy to get this set up
right now but
This is also the time for if you'd like to actually have your comment read on the screen
and that'd be great as someone would test that because your comment will come right on the screen.
It can be something terrible about me. Man, just don't use like terrible words. You know,
don't use TOS words. But, you know, say whatever you want to me. I can take it, you know, especially
because it will, you know, help me help the show have been, you know, ultimately not to deter anybody
But you can also keep it anonymous I get well I never have to know who it is
You know, it's like a few if you actually want you know, want to say something or you just want to be funny
Or you have a comment or you have a song request
My comment my passwords changed four months ago. Okay, I figured it out. Okay. Am I in the control panel select stream?
Oh, here I am
Okay, concurrent viewers one views three. Oh, no. Oh
No, oh, no, is that a good sign or not? I don't know. I don't know if this will be a big hit
Do you see this stuff on the screen?
Is it configured? Let me see.
And I need to set up my green screen.
Like I said, I might need a ladder.
I'm gonna have to look.
Because I had the ladders be on the stairs and stuff like that.
Oh my goodness.
You can go to cultofpsychee.com
and that is the power chat.
It should take you to like a page.
There.
Okay. Okay.
Working on the psychonomicon a little bit.
Let me just check how things look
See if I need to make any adjustments
But I can't wait to see how it works
It looks like it's up on the screen
Am I sitting too close to the screen? This is just too early
Okay, and I need to look at this
I'm still learning how to do like camera work. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Everything looks like it's good
I don't know but the chat like I don't know it looks like there was a chat on the screen
I don't know. I don't know. Is that a real chat? I was at the real time because I don't see any chat in the
The other anyway, yeah, okay, so yeah, I mean I was able to get this set up. Wow
I'm kind of proud of myself for how I did it
Because I still want to do a couple things to it. Maybe I can do those now
But it might come down while I'm doing it, but I'll try to do it anyway
I want to
Do a couple things
Okay, we'll see if it has time to do it. Okay. Here we go. Or it's my my personal assistant
I'm stew. Okay
So anyhow, I guess this format will be like, you know
Very popular is it cuz it's like I'm a second was like he's nightmares and it says cult of psyche cult of psyche is
Psychies nightmares affiliated. Okay. Well, I saw some things. I mean, I saw some things like I think I was watching
You know Alex had a great stream
About you know Carl and Mimi
Playing a clip and I guess and then salmon was on salmon. I mean, it's like they had a good a good
Energy chemistry. I mean, it's like, you know, he's always got so snoopy and stuff. But I mean, I like how she's been
handling
herself with some of these people
And you know and you try to bring me up and say oh, it wasn't psyche like a weirdo
Like I don't know it's like there's such a like a pull to like oh, let's make this person just a weirdo because
Then you know or because who they talk to or who who they who they like who their friend
It's like let's make people be afraid like it's like basically a tear campaign like really like oh like this person like that person now
About NorCal, I don't know if NorCal was trying to get me in trouble today or something like that
I didn't know he was firing an actual gun into his bushes and stuff
But I mean, I still don't think that that's against the TOS. I think that on live streams
You can as long as you're not pointing the gun at the screen or pointing at somebody else
I don't think that it's a problem and you can fire and everything because there's gun shows and there's I mean
there's all kinds of like gun channels and
So I know live streams have a slightly different rule about it, but you know, hey
I mean I've had people show their guns on the show before I mean, I don't think it's a big deal
I just say don't point it at the screen
So I don't know I've never seen a different rule than that
My hair is not greasy. It's just am I on in my life. I don't know no one's talking. Okay. Well, anyway, it's okay
Um, and this will be like, you know, not a stream yard stream.
And so if you want to get your voice heard, the best way to do it is probably
to, um, just use the TTS system, which is cultofpsychee.com.
And you can do everything anonymously.
And it's like a, you know, and it's all set up.
Um, it's called power chat.
I don't know if you've heard of power chat.
And so what will happen is if you send a message.
Then you will see your message put on the screen. I think you can do different voices
I might have to upgrade or something. I have to check it out to see I don't know
But I know I have some kind of funny voice. I'll read the thing
I know I know you know an Elisa's like, you know, I can do Hank Hill and she uses a system
And so I think it's a good way to monetize the channel too, especially while, you know,
I'm not officially monetized on YouTube. Hey, what's up? Corruption is real. Hey,
reality Nancy. Look, do you like the new graphical setup? I have a new graphical interface.
I would love someone to send a TTS. Like, well, you know, I know, I know it's like, you know,
I'm not like trying to grip or anything. I'm just saying, saying if you want to like test out the
system, that'd be really cool. I mean, I can like try to get trigger like a test and like
right now let's see if it works and we'll see what happens I'll see this is what happens I guess
when you when you send it when you send something um but uh let me see if I can do this okay
Might have to it's I'm like really busy with tasks. Yeah, good to see you though. Corruption is real good to see you
Yeah, so this is a non stream yard stream
But you know if there is a demand too for like a panel like I can just like start on start out here
And I can always go over to stream yard and stuff and
Yeah, I'm afraid of there right now. It's just like, uh, you know, but it's like, yeah
I'd like to just you look at this on the screen see like it says like share subscribe. So, um, yeah, there's cool things
I'm adding new features in I'm trying to add like a daily tarot card and
A daily and just show where the screen is have I been you've been working busy working
I'm pretty good. You see like you see like I'm I got a new tripod
shout out to
Alexandra at an IT2 Week Wiki, and IRL News Time, Streamer Analysis Channel, and Alexandra Mayers.
Thank you so much. This is perfect
I've tried to do a tripod setup before and especially like with the nuke and it was like it was like not so
But this one I was able to attach it like no problem
I did like kind of like I saw this guy
He was this Indian guy and he made like a clawed code into like a robot
you know, he put a robot as clawed code and
And he made it and had wheels and stuff, but he's like and I wonder and got the cheapest wheels
I mean, I'm sorry. I don't want to make it like a difficult accent, but he's like he went got the cheapest wheels
But then it wouldn't like turn, it wouldn't like, when you try to turn it, it would go back and forth, but they wouldn't like turn and pivot and stuff.
And so he's like, and so I just, I did the best thing possible.
And he's like, that's where the Scotch tape comes in and you just put Scotch tape over the wheels.
And so they would turn.
And I was like, that is pretty ingenious, like Scotch, so it's like, you know, sometimes there are like fixes that work just as well.
You know, it's only about most screwdrivers. Sometimes scotch tape can be an amazing thing, but I hope I'm doing this right
I did say I wanted like hook up. I want to set up the green screen behind me here
But it's like it is above like of stairs right there. And so it will be like a
journey
Attaching it it looks like a spirit is walking up the wall. Oh, I see something. Oh, that's yeah, that's like the wind or something
No, see that yeah, that's like something flapping in the wind. Yeah, I have like some curtains and stuff
But I think like there are some yeah, I saw something I saw that other weird thing that was kind of weird
That was the other side of me and I was going slowly up the wall
Saw that isn't that real there are spirits probably around the house
You know, it's like I know I get like the and it sometimes if you talk about it
Then it will start happening like at the lights will start flickering and stuff
Yeah, but I think that might have been like right there that I think that the great that right there is like part of the
Part of the curtain and stuff, but you know, there are there's that happens
Okay, so I'm gonna try to sit. Oh, look at the camera moves and stuff. Oh, is that me moving?
I'll speak to them a little bit behind. Okay
So let me see if I can send a test message because I'm trying to put other cool stuff on the screen
Okay. Oh, I'm okay. So now I'm at
I'm a
Okay, I'm shit out of luck on that one. I'm just happy that the case it seems like it's working
You've been seeing it since you were five years old. You've been seeing spirits. Wow
Yeah, so it will in a in Palm Springs. We had this happen. We have this we have a house in Palm Springs
it used to belong to Howard Hughes and
There's just been weird like it's in Palm Springs. And so it has spiritual energy there
It's a kind of wastes in the desert, right?
I think it's in Riverside County or something, but um, it's a good it's a good oasis
It's like a little and that's where the Hollywood people because it sounded like you can go to the desert
Which is like a whole like, you know, you can either go to like New Mexico or something. Yeah, so we had so we empowered use this house and
he
His spirit would come and like sit on the bed with like a certain
Women that would stay could stay at that like it's like the parents, you know, they're married friends and stuff like that and so
they would
Say that they woke up with a man staring at them, but he had long fingernails and hair
I don't know if that was that or I don't know if I think that was that's what well
I know he had long fingernails and hair like Howard. He's just kind of famous. He had this
He created a plane called a spruce goose. He was like a millionaire and he was very good-looking
But he had like paranoia about you're going home. Okay corruption is real come back soon
Yeah, and so he's already going crazy and he started growing his nails really long
He said he thought that there were germs and I think he said free mason's rule
I know something like that or that was the Simpsons. I'm gonna get me getting confused. Okay, but
Yeah, Howard because mr. Burns has played Howard Hughes in some episodes where he's like going crazy and stuff
You know, he gets really long hair and really long long fingernails and stuff
And so that was kind of a creepy thought like a man with like long fingernails.
And I know now I'm not favorite with my fingernails.
Look, hold on, you see him yet?
Yeah, you saw the plan he built.
That was huge.
They built around the plan, the plane.
Oh, OK.
So yeah, so it's like a spruce goose.
Yeah.
Well, this house is like a very nice.
You know who it's right next to you, too?
The neighbors are like Hannah Barbera and, you know, like,
and they always had this HB.
Gates on it, but it's like there's small accessible house
What the hell is that? Hello?
Hold on hold on I'm on the air hold on one second. I'm in second. I'm so sorry. Oh my god
I thought that was a TTS. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay. One second one second. I know it's not ringing
I'm on the air come say hi on the show. Oh my god. That's scared the hell out of me. Oh my gosh
Yeah, oh my gosh
Thought I was the TTS started or I thought there was a ghost or something. I see there's my nails
They looked good
Wow, that was scary watch about me and watch myself get scared to death right now
Because all of a sudden I heard a voice and it because it's my discourse. I'm like in a discord chat, but I
Yeah, we have that home. Yeah
We had it since I was little
Hey, is there a Dougie Doug? What's up? What's a Dougie Doug? You look I'm up. Do you see do you guys see the upgrade on the interface?
Okay. Yeah, I don't know. You still hear me. Okay. Good. I hope you can still hear
I don't know. I'm trying to turn off the discord, but I can't find it's like not the icon is not around
I mean, it's like it's it's I'm a mess over here, but um
Yeah, good to see Dougie Doug. Like, uh, yeah, I do like the
I need to put on a background. Oh, I can't like they don't have back. Oh, they do have backgrounds on this thing
Hold on. Let me put up a background
Web cam. No, no, okay. It almost I did the string cancel
What can I do here? I can like put up. Oh, okay
Managed channel of a site. It used to have like some kind of like
Like green screen I could do. I don't know if it's still here. Hold on. Thank you. Oh, you want to see pick?
You're gonna see pics of the house
Yeah
Let me see if I can find like some old pictures of it on from like the
You know, let me see if I can look at it if I go Howard Hughes Palm Springs home
Actually, wait, but we could drive by there. There's there's Elvis's house like my dad was a great tour guide
and
Yeah, let me see
It's very it's a small house, but it's like we used to go there for like vacations and it's like now
It's kind of like a family. They we think that it's that they've added added to the property and stuff
Okay. Yeah
Okay, so I'm looking right now and it's like saying oh there's a Howard. It says
There's another Howard or there's another Howard Hughes house
Says the best one is his residence in Palm Springs is a whitewashed brick mid-canon century home in Airby Cove
Okay, and that's called the Howard, but then it says
There's a separate historic Palm Springs property originally built in the 1940s by Howard Hughes
No one for its bungalows studios and garden setting the complex sits in the warm sands area
and over the years people of
completed the name in local lore because of the similar naming. It's named after primarily a
street name, properties here are not the same as the Arabic code room house and not the core.
So if you're chasing exact Howard's house on whatever the street,
what you're hitting is overlapping myths surrounding three different points.
at the, at the, when we have, it says, often, it says, it says, it's not his primary, it's
not his primary house, but he built it. I mean, it's like, and so, you know, and I guess
he would go to the property. I mean, I'm sure he's done, done time there too, you know,
it's like, but I don't know, kind of a cool story.
I don't know. I don't know what's all these noises are.
I mean, it's going to be crazy.
Okay. Let's see.
Yeah. Well, I mean, I've already on 40 minutes.
Like, you know, people are coming by and say,
I don't know if I'm extending too close.
I want to like fix the,
see if there's like a green screen I can do,
but now I
Now I can't like figure it out. I mean it's like cuz it's like I'm just used to
StreamYard but I remember I was doing effects and stuff on on thing but we'll
just have to do with this now. Now I am wearing my Speedo tonight and so if I
if I hit $10 I will stand up and show you guys but if not you will not see it
tonight and if someone wants to donate $20 so I will not stand up I will do that
All I want you to do is have fun. I just want everyone to have fun, but I'm wearing it and it's clean because I took a bath in it
Okay, and so it is clean
There is no marks. There's nothing embarrassing and nothing embarrassing about it. It's just pure
American pride
Yeah, and so I would bet the second I'll continue like talking about like what I was gonna talk about but I mean it's like I
Just like sometimes it's like people don't
Don't know. I'm just seeing it's like there's the people get a little bit
Howard he went crazy later in life locked himself in a room until he passed away. Yep. He did he did
Do you see you guys see your comments on the screen? Look your comments are on the screen
I need to maybe do it a little bit bigger. What do you think and make it maybe bolder so you can see him better and stuff
Let me make this big. Let me have me look how it looks
I'll have to close the chat one second
To the night owl tricks
Cosmic vibes
Where are these people?
He always know exactly what card to pull. I mean these sound like
Is that the chat?
That's I think that must be like a I don't think that's my
I
That's something I need to fix and they get the actual chat on the screen. Oh my gosh
I mean that's a little bit embarrassing
Have to say I'm so sorry. Let me just open up the regular chat. I think I have one like isn't that nice
It's like it's like a whole 1%
That's not the real chat. No, I know that's not I'm way too nice to be my chat. Yeah
The answer, you have a fan, Duggie Duggie is here.
Yeah, but what did you think?
I mean, it's like, I mean, I think someone was trying to get on, on Alex's show and
she's like has a way of burning her way of burning things and it's like, and she was
wanting to get back to this video.
And so after Sam and she kind of wrapped up and I don't know if like that person waited
or was still there or what happened exactly, but that person then then goes in and gets
all mad at her.
And then it says things about me start saying like, oh, you know, um, what, uh, but how,
how, what do you, well, I'm just saying, I said, I said, this like, this chat thing
until like, put the audience's chat and it looks like the chats that are coming up are
not the audience's chats.
I don't know.
Maybe there's like another, maybe I'm on my own.
I think these are from like Twitch or something like that.
I think those are Twitch names.
They must be from, I must, I must be.
Yeah, I'll just say someone wanted to get on the air with Alex and then I don't know she just moved on in the show
But then they can't they did this went over and then they got there and they started like you know bad
Mouthing her bad bouncing me and it's like
Whoa, I mean like whoa, I mean it's like just slow your roll like about that. You know, it's like
It's like this and I know it was probably out of like some kind of hurt feeling or something
But it's like I'm not I don't I'm not I don't hate people
I don't like hate anybody and so it's like I'll like just I don't listen. I'll hear people. I'll understand people
and
It's like but it's like it's kind of like
Just like be nice to be nice when people are nice to you be nice and like it. I was like, I don't know
You can see the chat on the screen
That was I think that that's my dream chat. That's that's my that's the chat. I wish I had I'm just kidding
I'm just so sorry guys. I'm so sorry. No, I love I know I love my chat. I love you guys
Most like 90% of my chat like absolutely love and that's why it will be fixed
I won't be able to fix it until 9 p.m. But I will be able to fix it tonight
I could try to ask Hermes to fix it, but I'm not sure.
Yeah, I have a few robots that work for me.
Like it went his name Hermes.
And Hermes probably can fix it,
but I don't want Hermes to mess up things
because I haven't having my other robot work on this.
My other robot, it's expensive.
And so, but I do have everything that kind of worked out.
So I'm on mostly free like APIs or I'm on credits.
And there's so many credits being given out right now
from Google.
There's hundreds of dollars of like
programs and credits you can like basically if you're the developer you know you go and find
into developer programs google they offer thousands of dollars of credits like you have to just make
sure you use them in the right time for like the thing it's like and then you can if you don't know
how to do this if it's so technical you can like ask ai how do you do this and like walk me through
it and it's like i'm so dumb i even i have to have it do it for me sometimes
Yeah, I mean do you want to see some of the you know, I mean the mini-man's interview is great
We can plug him. I don't know if I can play something on this song. I have to go on another show, but
But how do you like the how do you like the vibe though? I mean, I think I like how I like the look so far
I need the real chat coming on the screen
I need I want the Easter eggs and the I want the chat interaction and I want in there
But I do have the priceless right there. I think that website will take you if you I would love a TTS on the show
I mean, I and I can't send a TTS test right now. I mean, I can't but I don't know how to do it
I mean, it's like I have to figure it out and it's like
So I need my I need my robots to like my robots asleep and it's okay. It's okay
So
Should I do I don't know I mean I wish I could do the setup for stream yard
I mean it would be so ideal because she has its own graphic settings and all kind of cool stuff
You can do but I'd rather just I have stream yard and then have like that controls to do the media and stuff
Really easy and stuff, but then I have this
With the T with the TTS setup, I think that would be the best
And guys, I will play the songs too if you want like, you know most most songs, you know
Like for $5, you know, your song will just start playing, you know, it will start playing and
So
Yeah, I think I'm probably gonna try to stay on this stream until I hit the $10 speedo mark though
But um, do I have any coffee left? I do
This is my coffee I got today. It's a cheapy. It's like the
Out for free because I paid about it's been with my points my points
And so I have another sip of sip a little bit. I know net and Nancy
Nancy like a range the whole thing too
Yeah, I mean it's like here. I'll play some of the I see that's the thing I can't play the episode
I'm right. It's like I don't really know how to how to like
Share my screen here. Yeah, I need to figure some stuff out still
So maybe I'll be like back after nine o'clock or maybe I don't know see I want to oh my gosh
Look at chat overlay must be enabled in a streaming. I can have a chat overlay for I see
But I need premium don't I oh I need premium. Oh my gosh
okay, but
You will hear an alert sound
and alert
Don't know anyone want to test it out. I'm gonna enable media. Hold on. I'm not gonna show the media video
Chat you can select a voice. Okay. I have the font. I have everything. I don't know if is it overlaying
I don't I mean it's like I don't know if I'm missing it's if you sent something
Just let me know cuz I might have to test it at first. Okay, right?
Give Claude my stream key
No, I did give cloud my my snow cloud has my stream key. It's all I mean, that's all set up
But I was looking I was just looking at it has pro features
I'm not sure which one and then some of the stuff was turned off like the media was just turned off
So I just turned it on I've given it this the steam the stream key
What will it do for a fake layout? There's not even a real chat. I know this is called a test stream
SIG, okay, but and I'm paying for cloud pro. Yes, but I'm out of usage until 9 p.m. Okay
I know it's a fake layout. It's obvious it is, but it's just like for the aesthetic and testing, okay?
This is a test, Jim, and that's what I'm saying. And say, can you test the TTS and tell me what you really think of me?
If you want to talk anymore, you have to give me your advice through TTS.
You're paying, you still have limits. Yeah, well, I'm not paying for the $100 one. I'm paying for like the $20 one.
The $20 one, you know?
And so that's less like it, like it, you know, it poops out and especially if you use like the opus or the faster models, but they just had they just had something called, um, called fable and that I was using that and it goes really fast and it's really, really good.
But then it's like they took it away because it was too powerful for like normal people, I guess, but the government or the government actually told them to shut it down.
So does anybody like to send a TCS? I mean, I really appreciate it too because then what could I do?
I could probably buy a beard tonight if I had three or four dollars
Otherwise, I uh, I have nothing all these scammers and our names Sam pay attention. Oh, you know
Sam Altman
Sam man's bank fried. Yep. Yeah, but my name is not Sam
Not even my initials
My initials are JRB
No Arby's jokes about you know roast beef sandwiches and vaginas, please
Okay, I'm nice. Hmm. I wonder if we'll get if we'll get a TTS though
But tell me if you send a TTS and it doesn't go through and I'll I'll say it and I'll do it in dramatic voice
Nancy shh. I look like I've got to Arby's and gets the steak nuggets
How are my teeth tonight?
But say I'm like I'm on a tripod today though. Look I'm on a new tripod and so
Oh my god, my teeth look terrible. That's something in my teeth. It's like I guess it's a lighting
I look like I have a brown tooth. I don't oh
Oh my god, I have something in my teeth
Never mind. Oh
What is that?
Hmm, it's that stupid tobacco these these switcher sweets are gonna be the death of me my nails are terrible because of them
My teeth are terrible smoking is just bad
I have leaves in my teeth. I do. I like these fucking tobacco leaves in my teeth
Hey, sick. This one's I'll do this for you. This is for you sick. Yes
I'm in a speedo and yes, I said I was gonna wait for ten dollars
But I'm trying to get the ball rolling here. I I'm not gonna not yeah
Well, I'm not a pregnant woman nor will I ever be so, you know, but it's time to join the stream
I know Canada. Do you like it? I mean, I mean, I I was hoping um, you know, Harry would be here
I have a crush on this guy named Harry. Harry Tazikas
Tatsuyakis and
I just have a song about him. I wrote
People think you're scary
But I love
Your bunghole anyway. I love Harry. Oh my gosh. He's like Joe Rogan without the money or looks
I mean, I love it. I mean all I want is the voice. I just want Joe Rogan's voice
Yeah, that's a liar. Yeah, a Greek liar Harry. He would burn me. I know. Well, I mean, I would I would have to scam him
I mean, it's like there's no way I'd let him scam me
Seiki stole some old Chinese ladies method of income. What playing the look playing the Greek liar
I'm a bum. Oh my god. I'm so sorry. Oh my god. What am I high? I wish
Do you have like a look my vape is like honest like last dregs?
Well, I told you I'm wearing a speedo. I'm trying guys
Where's the dough? No, why aren't the dough nose running at my legs are like a hot dogs?
That's rude
Beedah has a gafer
What does that mean? I don't even think I want to know what that means. I'm smoking a vape
This is called a I don't know what kind of vape this is, but I'm gonna try another hit on them
I didn't have it right here. She's showing you. Oh my god
See, it's almost not it's on his last dregs
Harley got me say Harley got me high at all, but how are we doing on that? Let's see
Are the power chats ruling it? I want to hear somebody on the microphone now
I want to test it. I'm gonna have to ask Hermes if it can test it for me
Hermes comes through most of the time
I'll try to get it to fix the chat so the actual chat shows on the screen too
But I don't know if Hermes can like do this right now. It might be a job for Claude, but okay
I'm gonna ask Hermes about it.
Okay, I'm asked, I asked my robot to work on it.
Okay, but oh my God, see it's like the top,
it's like so small, like how could anybody ever see that?
I need to have like that fixed, like to make it bigger.
I wonder if I can like that beat it on?
Oh, I don't have a stream yard on,
but I don't think beat is even here.
It's beat in the chat, I think I might have it blocked.
I don't think she's on but uh you know maybe I'll do a mass unbanned let me see what Hermes is saying
yeah it's working on it okay we'll see we'll see I just wanted to make sure it works I mean
then you maybe you'll see how exciting it is when like it goes on the screen the whole message reads
you can say anything you want almost I mean it's like you know there's probably certain words you
shouldn't use but whatever else you want to say to me like be creative you know finally it will be heard
Is she banned? I don't know. I can see if she's banned. Hold on a second.
She hasn't done meaning. I don't think she's banned in the chat.
Well, Brandon was saying he's banned in my chat and stuff.
I look into it.
Okay, community moderation.
User management.
Okay, so let's see who's in the ban list.
Tell me if anybody should be unhidden.
Chat rat.
Totally not Aiden.
Aiden 23.
Crack Rock Benny, Aiden the completionist, Ben HK Gleck, Ignorance is Bliss, Charlie,
Israeli YouTube Investigation Team, Kevin, ICU, Lowell Cowhunter, David David David,
David David, Psyche loves cherds, Lady Bathory, YouTube Help Administration, Discount, Aiden the Destroyer, Tucker Dick, Concrete Larry III, Joe's Mother Loves Blacks, Cheese Snorter Aiden, BigBatCate, Kotsch and Mattel, Gainville did nothing wrong, Manly Man Aiden,
Team all I mean this person that says some of these people Cheta Bob slob
Concrete Larry, Jr.
Cult of psychos copium dealer Aiden concrete Larry David zoo loves lady boys
Bong Bong the troublemaker David
One Amy David juice the one of many ETC simps black RG
Allied master computer
Carhartt beanie
Psyche's Fleas, Banana Eatin' Chimp, Poppy Tender,
Lady's Subbi, Dave Fitzgerald, Norman Bates, Viv,
Chicken Bunny Aiden, David, David, Brandon's Massive Tits,
Adair Gerald's, Tay-Tay, David, Jim John Haywire,
Yellow Snowman, Mike K Hunt, so nice to meet ya.
J.B. David, David, David, David, David, Reverse, Delareeva, a fed named Fred, Michelle Bighams.
Oh, they're okay. Brandon was hidden. Oh, he's unhidden. Okay. Okay. Giant Shrimp, Fifth
Sage, Art, Concrete Larry IV, Udder, Charlie, Big Purr, David, David, My God, Aiden, Sack,
Psyche loves turds, Katie Crip Aiden, Concrete Larry the Six, Spam King Aiden, Artichoke,
and LA always feels like.
Anybody, there's some good people on the list, Mass Unban.
Well, I mean, but like 90% of the list is like Aiden and Concrete Larry and Allied Master
So I don't want to unban him. I mean, oh, okay. I'll unban the big bat cake because of that name gives me a chuckle
I mean, but I don't know. It's a big bad cake. I think it was a dick. Okay, both still, okay
I'm gonna keep that David person
How about Uter Big Purr? I don't think I like that person. No, I don't think I like that like this sage at all
Don't trust our band delay giant shrimp big. I don't afraid a fed named Fred. No
Nice try. Tay-tay. Okay. Tay-tay. I'll let on back on. Okay. Tay-tay
Psyche's please no black RG. I will unban from the chat
Zoo loves lady boys. Does anybody know zoo loves lady boys? Anybody named Aiden or concrete Larry?
No, I'm gonna I'm gonna unblock big back Kate. I'll consider Tucker dick
Lady Bathory, I mean all she does is say horrible things. I don't know
I'll unban the little cow hunter that feels safer and that kind of person
I
See you. I mean, I just don't like that name. I don't like that name crack. I know no, okay
I think that's enough in the chat chat rat. No
Okay, I fixed it
I think I fixed it everybody.
Let me see, did a donation come on the screen?
Let me see what's going on with Hermes right now.
No browser sources currently configured OBS for chat.
Okay, so I'm working on the chat thing right now.
So that's part of the reason it's not right
because I'm working on it.
But I need to be on live to figure this stuff out, you know?
And then I'm gonna do the,
oh yeah, so I need to like log it into Power Chat.
Okay, hold on a second.
She needs a video ID. Let me see if I can get that. Let's see if I can get this working
Hermes is amazing. I would say if you want like to
Start with something like it's better to use Hermes
Here, let's see if this works. Oh shit
Because Hermes is basically you can run it for free, right? Okay
Think that's it. I think I okay, so I think it's I think it's figuring it's like I didn't mean to tell the information
I figured out it's on its own before I needed it to do it. So it's pretty good. Oh my gosh. Hi, rude
What are you doing? You like to be pet? Oh
Hi
Hey, is it okay the old man cat really? I'm in a speedo. You know, I'm in a speedo
Yes, I'm wearing a speedo
Not nude
Get your minds out of the gutter. Okay
So, oh, where am I? Okay?
So let me see I need I think I need to log into power chat for this them Hermes to figure it out
Oh, so I need to go to power chat. Oh account settings. Oh my gosh. I'm not even logged in. Okay. Oh, here it is
I am logged in. Okay. Okay. I just need to tell Hermes. I'm sorry technical difficulties
But see how I'm popular and people won't even the pay to like tell me they hate me
I mean, it's like, you know, but I did unban a bunch of people. So it's working on it. It's working on it
some progress there's okay any who we'll see if it starts working we'll see if it starts working
you like te te yeah that was rude well i mean it's like look i've been on for i can see for
i don't know how long i've been on but i know it's what time it is it's 7 40 p.m. yeah i know i mean
it's like see i don't know why he would do that um nancy like you know i think he just has an anger
You know, I think it's everyone's out to get them and stuff and things that took me on a conspiracy
That was like me. I mean, I I don't know. It's getting a little
Ridiculous, I'm just saying like we were good to him like and so it's like he I mean if he has a problem
Like he could like just like, you know, I way I've said
Hello to him on a show and stuff and I mean, I don't know I unbanned him just now. So yeah, that's really oh my gosh
So what should I do? I mean, but then I say I start getting like, you know, hi and stuff and like
Let's see what's Hermes doing. Okay. Yeah, we're okay. Okay. Let's see if this works. It's firing a
test alert. It just works. I'm just gonna like, I think it looks pretty good. I like the setup. I
like how much closer I am to it. It's like I'm not so far away. I'm like, you know, you can see
like kind of close my face and I hope you enjoyed like this little bit more of an intimate, oh,
there it goes. Okay. Did the chat ever hook up right? No. Okay. Well, I'm gonna keep
said something completed hold on a second
okay okay i need to go give me okay hold on okay hold on i need to bind it myself hold on
okay creator tab and select testing okay i don't see that i mean i have an assistant though okay
oh it's working it looks like the test chat you just sent from power tights and showing up in your
Okay, yeah
Well, where can I say okay? I'm sorry. This is very unprofessional
Okay, let me yes. Yes. Yes. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
I mean, I love when it like Brian just says, okay, should I just do it? Like that's what that's what I love
I mean, it's like I can't believe it asks you so much like I have to beg for it to do stuff sometimes and it's like
It's like no, I can't I can't I can't please can you get I was like I'm too dumb to figure out and it will do it for me
Not lose you. I just
If I knew how to do it, I wouldn't be asking like the,
I just like, I'm bad with like little details sometimes.
I'm not gonna get under the blanket.
Like I promise I won't get under the blanket,
but I mean, I'm gonna put my legs under it
because now they're cold so I'm just bringing a speedo.
If I, no, I would leave.
Okay, so take, send a test to alert, okay.
Send random tests to, let's have it that.
Is this working?
Enable test viewer counts, okay.
Send tests to alert.
Okay, let's see.
i'm saying youtube i'm saying power chat okay so are we seeing anything guys are we seeing
anything on the screen was there emoji so the chat come up okay okay well anyway that was a test
stream i would say it was mildly successful it was i mean it's like i got the graphical interface
of i don't care for not having extreme art available at my disposal i don't like how the chat is not
But I have to wait a few minutes to fix it. I'm gonna meditate for a little bit after 9 o'clock 9 p.m
I will go back online and we'll see if I get a donation. I will get a couple drinks
Because I had my my out that I haven't McDonald's I just got the free coffee. Well, I'll be fine
Okay, thank you guys. Hey, thank you everybody
I'll get this fixed and sort it out and appreciate you being here
Thanks for coming to the chat and oh hi. Hi, babe. You didn't so nothing triggered or anything like nothing
I said like send a test and stuff and so it's not working
If anybody sends anything, I'm so sorry. I'll read your chat. I'll read your thing or play your video or whatever
But no one said anything and so and I didn't see beat it in the chat. So I don't know about that and
Let me see if it's doing anything.
Okay, I'll have to wait a little bit for this.
I'm gonna have it all pimped out, guys.
I'm gonna have it all pimped out.
I'm gonna have it all personalized, pimped out.
All the nightbot commands you can use.
I'll have fun stuff on the screen.
I mean, it looks, I like how it's going already.
Like I like having like this really like, you know,
my neon theme and it's got my prices
and the services list and, you know, it's tough.
We'll see, we'll see what happens.
But anyway, you have a nice night, and I'll see you later, okay?